This arrow is irreplaceable.
There's only one, you know.
It's essential to my mission.
And losing it is not an option.
Hey, leave that arrow alone!
He'll bleed out if you keep it up!
Because of the failings
of my blockhead brother,
I now have no other
choice but to kill you.
Nothing personal, but I can't
let anything happen to the arrow.
It wouldn't do for it to break or
catch the eye of some old crone.
Given my meticulous nature,
I feel somewhat compelled to
return it to its proper place.
I mean, what should one do when
one is finished listening to a CD?
You should put the first in its
case before listening to the next.
That's how everyone does it.
And it's how I do things.
Now what's this?
So you've decided to enter our abode.
No shit, Sherlock!
How else was I supposed to beat your
smarmy ass and get Koichi back to normal?
Hm.
Brother!
Don't count me out just yet!
Wait for me to help before
you attack him! Attack?
I hope you're ready!
This fight is just getting started!
There's something moving
up there in the dark.
What the hell?
GASP
But today I'm going to be a
little bit more than a day.
I'm going to be a little
bit more crazy noise.
I'm going to be a little bit more.
Okuyasu!
Your stupidity is truly astounding.
If you hadn't stumbled in
here like a bumbling idiot,
worse company would have
already destroyed Josuke.
And what's more, you walked
right into the line of fire.
But bro, I...
Your stand, the hand, may be menacing,
but you, little brother, are a fool.
The incompetent will hinder
the capable without fail.
I've told you over and
over since we were kids.
And life is only worth
living when it has growth.
You've heard that before, too.
I've never seen wounds like those before.
What kind of attack leaves
you looking like a pincushion?
One thing's for sure.
He's hiding something.
Poor little brother. You know,
it's idiots like you who deserve to
die like a miserable roach on its back!
He's fiddling the place with tiny holes!
What is he doing?
Shining Diamond!
What kind of monster attacks
his own freakin' brother?
Josuke Higashikata.
No matter how dire the situation,
he would never abandon this brat.
I'm willing to bet he'll be
back to save him soon enough.
He'll die by my hand.
As will anyone who gets in
the way of this bow and arrow.
I'll wipe them all out of existence!
Now then, I think it's way past time
you tell me about your brother's stand.
What kind of power does his stand have?
Spill it and I'll get rid
of these holes in your face!
Like I tell, I'll never rat
my bro out. Understand? Fool!
Have it your way.
I suppose.
That's just how it's gonna be.
Alright, I'm going in.
Since you're not gonna help,
just stay out of my way, Okuyasu.
Koichi doesn't have much time,
so I have to move quickly.
If earlier is any indication, his stand's
gonna attack from somewhere in the dark.
One thing's for sure, this is gonna suck.
I have to rely on instinct.
Senses don't fail me now.
Where are you going?
I gotta know, Josuke, why the
hell did you heal my injuries?
Be quiet, let me focus.
Didn't it cross your mind
that I might attack you?
I am your enemy, after all.
Are you serious?
That depends on how
you answer my question.
Why the hell did you heal me?
I'm having a hard time piecing things
together, so hurry up and tell me, damn it!
Also, what the hell happened to your hand?
Did my bro do that to you when
you were pulling me out here?
None of this is making any sense.
Why'd you go through so much
trouble to try and save me?
Well, it's not complicated.
I didn't think anyone needed to die today.
Truth be told, it's as simple as that.
Koichi...
He was taken upstairs.
I'm not finished asking questions, Josuke!
Have you lost your goddamn mind?
I'm trying to rescue Koichi!
I wanna know why!
Why didn't you use your stance healing
power to patch up those holes in your hand?
Instead of wrapping it like that,
you could just make it all
better, like you did my face!
Unfortunately, that's not how it works.
Shining Diamond can't heal my own wounds.
The fact of the matter is, life isn't
always as easy as we want it to be.
While we're on the subject, I can't bring
back the dead no matter how hard I try.
Last thing, Okuyasu.
I don't know how Koichi's doing,
but if he doesn't pull through, I'm
gonna take it out on your brother.
So if shit hits the fan, be pissed off at
your bro, cause all of this is his fault.
Understand me?
If so, go outside and wait.
Koichi!
Shit, this has to be a trap.
He'll probably ambush me as
soon as I get close to Koichi.
But...
Even if it is a trap, this may
be my only chance to save him!
His life is on the line, so
there's no time to hesitate!
What?
Damn you bastard!
Yosuke!
We teleported.
I'm not the smartest guy in the world.
And I think with my
heart instead of my head.
I'll repay you for what you
did for me just this once.
That's where my gratitude ends.
I'm not helping you out anymore,
but I won't help my bro either.
This is it.
Well, that's great to hear, Okuyasu.
Hey!
You held up pretty great
back there, Koichi.
I'm so thrilled to see you're awake.
How many fingers do you see?
Uh, five.
I remember my neck being
slammed hard between the gates.
After that, I was...
Where the heck are we?
Sorry to have to tell you this, Koichi,
but things haven't gotten any
better while you were napping.
All I want to do right now is walk down
those stairs and leave this place behind.
But something tells me Okuyasu's
bro won't exactly comply with that.
There's no mistaking it.
Something's lurking up there,
but it's staying out of sight.
What the?
Something ran across that beam.
Josuke, what's going on here?
Koichi, I know you just woke up
and none of this makes sense,
but for now I need you to keep
quiet and stay close to me.
It was a hell of a lot creepier
when I couldn't see it.
Getting a look at it is actually a relief.
Looks like we've got a
pesky runt on our hands.
As soon as that little shit shows himself,
I'll blast him to kingdom
come with shining diamond.
Then we'll get the hell out
of here as fast as we can.
There you are!
What?
There's a ton of those things!
And they're all in some kind of uniform!
What the...?
It's like we're being ambushed
by a bunch of toy paratroopers.
This is the power of
Okuyasu's brother's stand.
Dammit!
Son of a...
I got a few, but taking out two or
three of them isn't going to be enough.
They leave tiny wounds, but the
damage definitely packs a wallop.
If we don't play this smart, we're
going to be in major trouble.
Since my idiotic little brother decided
to meddle with my trap and save that brat,
my plan has gone off the rails somewhat.
But in the grand scheme,
it's of little consequence.
You'll never escape this house.
or the domination of my perfectly
synchronized stand, Worst Company!
So his stand is called Worst Company.
Hey, Josuke, what's
going on? Ask me later.
I know it's crazy, but
I need you to stay back.
They're up to something.
All units, halt!
Ready, aim!
Fire!
Clare to base!
Head on.
These little bastards have the
firepower to blow us to smithereens.
Luckily, we've got windows.
I know we're on the second floor,
but we've got to break those
windows and jump to safety.
So much for that idea.
That's just great.
They've even got helicopters, but how's
his stand taking the form of U .S.
Army Apache choppers?
Watch your back!
They've got a tank!
You're right, those are definitely tanks.
Koichi, careful. Wait!
Do you want to run that
by me one more time?
Can you actually see the enemy?
The soldiers, tanks,
helicopters, all of them?
I don't understand what's
going on, but I can see them.
The arrow.
Since it didn't kill you, it
must have given you a stand.
Oh, so the Shrimp has one as well.
He's finally got the power to use a stand.
This certainly is a surprise.
It's the man of the hour, Okuyasu's bro.
This is a pretty ballsy move.
Showing off your stand like that?
You can think of my stand worse
company as a cast iron defense.
It renders all attacks and intruders incapable
of penetrating its protective shield.
I know you're itching to
put me out of commission,
but sadly, it's a pipe dream
that will never come to fruition?
as your shining diamonds attacks
will never get anywhere close to me.
Feast your eyes on this.
The perfect symmetry of my army's
formation is simply stunning, isn't it?
All units, maintain
battle formation at ease!
There's just nothing quite like having
everything beautifully in place.
Though you did destroy a few of my foot
soldiers with your attack, so my troops'
formation is irritatingly
asymmetrical now. Huh.
Well, you did say you were meticulous.
But did you really need to come out of
your hiding spot to tell us all that?
Now, what on earth would
give you that idea?
I came out here to observe
the little troublemaker.
You mean me?
Indeed I do.
If I recall, Koichi was your name.
Ironic that you appear to have the
innate ability to utilize a stand,
Manifest your stand right now and
show me the extent of its power.
If today's my lucky day,
you may just possess the ability
I've spent so long trying to uncover.
Show me your power and
I'll allow you to live.
But I don't know.
And what ability would that be?
It's about time you told
us what your endgame is.
I'll be asking the questions around here.
Do I make myself clear, Jazz King?
Keep in mind, I still
have you in my crosshairs.
You should be thanking me for
letting you live as long as I have.
That's just great.
Let's go! Get a move on!
Manifest your stand!
What's a stand?
Sorry, I have no clue what you mean. Huh?
It's your first time?
Well, I'll be.
Very well, Josuke.
Be a sport and show him
how to manifest his stand.
What?
The striking range of your Shining
Diamond is only a measly one meter.
It's a long shot, but if this wimp's stand
can compensate for the weakness of yours,
You might have a real chance
at escaping my company.
Good point.
A stand that could kick your ass would
be an awesome addition to the party.
Okay, materializing your
stand is easy, Koichi.
Ramp up the urge to protect yourself.
Or maybe think about pummeling
this guy until he's black and blue.
The rest boils down to instinct.
A stand unique to your spiritual
energy should reveal itself.
Hold on! Say what?
What?
You can't just bring that on me
and expect me to know what to do!
You don't know what to do?
Then please allow me to help you out.
Here's some inspiration.
Do it, Green Beret!
What? That's it?
Hey, Koichi, you have to try moving it.
What are you talking about?
The stand!
Now open your eyes!
What stand?
Are you saying I made this thing?
Yeah, I'll congratulate you later.
First, we need to find out what
this egg-shaped thing can do.
What it can do?
I don't know what the heck you
think is supposed to happen,
but I don't have any energy left!
That was the best I could do!
You're kidding!
That's it? Mm-hmm.
This stand.
Enough!
I've seen everything that I need to!
All units, get in battle formation!
Koichi, withdraw your stand!
If they destroy this egg, you'll die too!
What do you mean?
I don't know how to do that!
Light him up, men!
Aaaaah!
Your... Josuke!
Excellent!
Those two have been separated.
The crack in that egg.
The brat doesn't realize it, but
he might have something there.
So the only man dying today is Josuke.
Word to the wise, Sergeant bro. So,
if you're trying to bring the roof of this
dump down on our heads in a fiery inferno,
then do it and stop playing around!
This is great.
Yeah, I'm in the mood for a brawl.
Josuke Higashikata,
is it true that you strongly disapprove of
disparaging remarks related to your hair?
Why don't you find out for yourself?
Go on, I dare you!
Thanks, but I don't think
that'll be necessary.
Instead, I'll blow your head right off
from underneath that prized hair of yours!
Consider yourself forewarned!
But first-worst company will
fire bullets into your legs.
That'll keep you from running away.
Next, we'll focus on taking out your arms.
Once that's done, you'll have
no means of defending yourself.
Giving me Card blanche to blow
your brains and hair into oblivion.
Well, that sounds like a bulletproof
plan if I ever heard one.
If you overlook the fact that
it's completely impossible...
I've already told you how meticulous I am.
When I declare something, I stick to it.
Thus, the warning.
He's wide open.
All I have to do is make that
stand thing appear again.
It's only an egg,
but if I can somehow hurl it
at him and make a direct hit?
I might be able to beat him.
All right, Koichi, time
to rise to the occasion.
I'm gonna beat him.
Remember,
the only reason I'm still letting you draw
breath is because your stand intrigues me.
Bastard.
All units aim, fire at will.
Hey, Sergeant Bro,
have you ever heard the
story where Moses parts
the waters of the Red Sea
right down the middle?
Because that's what I'm about
to do to your pathetic army.
Then I'm going to beat you down.
My plan is proceeding
exactly as I forewarned!
But you're too big of a fool to see it?
Josuke Higashikata.
A landmine?
First, your legs will go.
Now, Apaches, release your
firepower and disable him!
He got my arm.
First the legs, then the arms.
Exactly as I predicted.
Hellfire is going to rain down
on you with a flurry of bullets!
Can those wounded arms of yours save you?
or will worse company tear you apart?
Let's find out as it fires
every missile shell and round!
You lose, Josuke Higashikata!
All units!
Ready, aim!
And what exactly do
you think you're doing?
Could it be you're accepting your fate?
Or is it that you're asking
me to show you mercy?
Well, no can do.
All you nerds take him out!
You think you've got me cornered, but
I've already implemented my tactics.
What?
I'm sure those are the missiles
I shot at Josuke's arm.
He turned them against me!
What, did you forget?
My Shining Diamond's special ability is to
repair almost anything that's been broken.
Really, if you're that forgetful,
you might want to take some notes
and make sure you're meticulous.
Any time I need to see a
face, it has closed my eyes,
and I am checking to a
base with a crystal mind,
a magenta feeling, check a
chapter in the face of my spine,
straight like a chicken cherry cola.
I don't need to try to
explain, I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face Of
the humic and the ball that I need to,
I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
Ooh, I got it if I need you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
But ooh, I'm trying to find you.